You know, people ask me all the time, I mean, how'd you get so confident? How'd you get so
fearless? And it was gymnastics. And we need our young black women to continue to be confident and
fearless. And if gymnastics is the path they choose, then we need to support them in it.
So I want you all to join in the Brown Girls Do Gymnastics fundraiser to help support black girls
who are competing in gymnastics. As you know, these sports ain't cheap. So we as a community need to
put our money forward and support our young women who are doing not just the flips, not just the
twists, but in that process, are learning discipline, are learning courage, are learning teamwork,
regimen, and all the things that we are going to need to continue to strengthen community moving
forward. Now let's see if I still got it. It's a Brown Girls Do Gymnastics event season. This is bigger
than gymnastics. This is about access. We are launching our $5 play. $5 to the Isla Foundation. The Isla
Foundation provides access to marginalized athletes, especially in the sport of gymnastics. Supports
programming and athlete experiences. Your $5 helps fund scholarships. It helps sustain the
museum masses. We have over 100,000 people in our community. We can exceed our $75,000 goal.
Just $5. $5. Just $5. Real impact. Click the link. Go to the link. Make the pledge and share it for it.
Let's keep access alive. Support our Brown Girls Doing Gymnastics.